<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lucas Leme</title>
<link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/feed/index.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description></description>
<generator>quarto-1.3.450</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>The Trial of Crypto’s Golden Boy: Things Sam Is Testifying About</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>With the jury in attendance, Sam Bankman-Fried took the stand to testify in his defense. Rachel Humphreys and Caitlin Ostroff break down where his story of the FTX collapse has differed from the testimony of his former colleagues Caroline Ellison and Nishad Singh.Further Reading:- What’s Happening Today at the Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Further Listening: - The Trial of Crypto’s Golden Boy  Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a741d0126a0be28cc82a874e3" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Ibovespa tem queda de 1,29%, e Vale fica entre as poucas altas desta sexta</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.bloomberglinea.com/resizer/1BFx52ga6H4VVpxgy8HLOCOueG0=/1024x0/filters:format(webp):quality(75)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/bloomberglinea/3D7WBJSP25HKPOF4CDADY37YQI.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Na semana, o principal índice da bolsa brasileira ficou praticamente estável. Nesta sexta, papel da mineradora subiu 3,48% após anúncio de dividendos e recompra de ações&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.bloomberglinea.com/resizer/1BFx52ga6H4VVpxgy8HLOCOueG0=/1024x0/filters:format(webp):quality(75)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/bloomberglinea/3D7WBJSP25HKPOF4CDADY37YQI.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Boomers? Millennials? BofA tem uma geração preferida na hora de investir em ações</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.bloomberglinea.com/resizer/U90aSWsOcNRc5F6HMa96pffsCwQ=/1024x0/filters:format(webp):quality(75)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/bloomberglinea/ICEURJHSNBCCPFYBSO7NFGYWEM.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Banco americano recomenda ações de empresas expostas a gerações mais velhas, conforme juros altos melhoram rendimentos da renda fixa nos Estados Unidos&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:30:02 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.bloomberglinea.com/resizer/U90aSWsOcNRc5F6HMa96pffsCwQ=/1024x0/filters:format(webp):quality(75)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/bloomberglinea/ICEURJHSNBCCPFYBSO7NFGYWEM.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>TikTok Wants to Be More Like Amazon. Amazon Wants to Be More Like TikTok.</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>TikTok is launching its Shop feature in the U.S. after mixed success in other countries. Meanwhile, Amazon’s Inspire feature brings short-form video to its shopping app. WSJ’s Meghan Bobrowsky on why the two companies are taking pages from each other’s playbooks.   Further Listening: -How TikTok Became the World’s Favorite App  -The Billionaire Keeping TikTok on Your Phone   Further Reading: -Amazon Confronts a New Rival: TikTok   Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a8987f4533ff88ee624f81a5d" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>#68 | O futuro do Ibov, novos riscos da Petrobras e o efeito devastador da Shein</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>CUIDE DA SUA BARBA COM A Dr. JONES (15% OFF COM O CUPOM MMAKERS15)! 👇 https://drjones.vc/mmakers🔴 Vale a pena investir no fundo Ibiuna Long&amp;amp;Short, que vai reabrir 30/out? Veja a análise neste link: https://lp.mmakers.com.br/relatorio-ibiuna-long-short-melhores-fundosSim, existe muita coisa boa pra comprar na bolsa brasileira enquanto o dinheiro está sendo sugado pelas Treasuries dos EUA.Nossos dois convidados (Aline Cardoso, head de research do Santander, e André Lion, gestor de ações da Ibiuna) mostraram onde estão suas grandes convicções neste momento. Petrobras aparece como preferida de ambos, mas eles divergem de empresas como Localiza e Rumo.Tivemos tempo para entender o que há por trás de toda queda de Soma e Centauro, o “segredo” de Mercado Livre e as melhores pedidas no setor financeiro. Ao final do programa, cada um fez sua projeção de qual será a grande estrela da bolsa em 2024. Apresentação: Thiago Salomão (@_salomoney) e Renato Santiago (@renatosantiago)Convidados: Andre Lion, gestor de ações da Ibiuna, e Aline Cardoso, head de research do Santander Edição: Bianca BarsottiAnuncie no Market Makers: https://sl.mmakers.com.br/mmk03t-conectar/</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a6362d732d2c0b51d4cdf6d77" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Money Talks: The future of crypto, part two</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Last week, we spoke to the author Michael Lewis, who was embedded with Sam Bankman-Fried, as FTX, the crypto-trading empire he built, came crashing down amid allegations of fraud, which Mr Bankman-Fried denies. Mr Lewis credits Changpeng Zhao - the boss of Binance, a rival exchange - with bringing Mr Bankman-Fried to prominence. But CZ, as he’s known, may also have played a role in his downfall. This week, we speak to him about what the future holds for crypto. Hosts: Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Tom Lee-Devlin. Guests: CZ.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer. If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit our FAQs page or watch our video explaining how to link your account.</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a2402e39b8101289c0b13f217" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Money Talks: Welcome to Economist Podcasts+</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>A special mini episode to welcome you to our subscription service. Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ before October 31st for 50% off. If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit our FAQs page or watch our video explaining how to link your account.</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a28fd9c6302e126c71fa85ffd" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Powell, Introductory Remarks</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Speech At the 2023 Daniel Patrick Moynihan Lecture on Social Science and Public Policy, hosted by the American Academy of Political and Social Science, Washington, D.C.</description>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.remessaonline.com.br/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/o-que-e-fed-1170x781.jpg.optimal.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>MAGAZINE LUIZA (MGLU3): MENOS DE R$ 2,00 EM 2023 | ESTÁ BARATA?</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>O Magazine Luiza (MGLU3) está hoje num momento completamente diferente do que viveu anos atrás. Entre 2015 e 2020, a ação da empresa saltou 93.000%, chegando a ser avaliada em R$ 160 bilhões. Mas nos três anos seguintes, a ação foi ladeira abaixo: 71% de queda em 2021, 62% em 2022 e 41% em 2023 até esse momento. No primeiro semestre de 2023, a Magalu acumula prejuízo de R$ 493 milhões, 83% acima do que reportou no mesmo período de 2022. Analistas esperam que a receita da varejista feche 2023 em R$ 38,2 bilhões, um número que parece bem expressivo mas é praticamente o mesmo do ano passado. Sem melhora nas vendas e com uma piora no resultado financeiro, a expectativa é que ela feche o ano com R$ 730 milhões de prejuízo, segundo projeções compiladas pela Bloomberg. Essa piora acompanha o momento bastante turbulento do setor varejista, com várias delas passando por sérias dificuldades de honrar as suas dívidas. Isso explica por que 10 em cada 10 espectadores do nosso YouTube pede para nós explicarmos o que se passa com a empresa da Lu e se ela está barata ou não. Então, no Mercado Aberto de hoje, vamos falar sobre tudo sobre a história e o momento atual do Magazine Luiza. O que você vai aprender neste Mercado Aberto:- O que faz e como o Magazine Luiza ganha dinheiro - Por que a ação subiu 93.000% de 2015 a 2020 - Situação atual da empresa (MGLU3) - O risco da varejista quebrar - Magazine Luiza é uma oportunidade? Deixe seu comentário abaixo para respondermos no próximo Mercado Aberto!Apresentação: Thiago Salomão (@_salomoney) e Matheus Soares (@maatsoares) Edição: Bianca BarsottiAnuncie no Market Makers: https://sl.mmakers.com.br/mmk03t-conectar/</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8adbe7feec5aac17581d324c2c" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Little Flaws</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Daniel Kahneman says, &quot;The long-term success of a relationship depends far more on avoiding the negative than on seeking the positive.&quot;It&#39;s like that in so many areas of life. Most people know what they&#39;re good at, or at least they think they do. Flaws, though, tend to be nuanced, and we&#39;re often blind to them. This episode shares dozens of little flaws I often think about -- ones that are easy to ignore, but can compound into disasters over time.</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a31625160ddb282e12cf71f98" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>BC - Focus - Relatório de Mercado - 20/10/2023</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>O Relatório Focus resume as estatísticas calculadas considerando as expectativas de mercado coletadas até a sexta-feira anterior à sua divulgação. Ele é divulgado toda segunda-feira. O relatório traz a evolução gráfica e o comportamento semanal das projeções para índices de preços, atividade econômica, câmbio, taxa Selic, entre outros indicadores. As projeções são do mercado, não do BC.</description>
  <category>Bacen</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://s2-oglobo.glbimg.com/4Ugd1L8ibkhIE19fug0Uch8n_yI=/0x0:2000x1323/888x0/smart/filters:strip_icc()/i.s3.glbimg.com/v1/AUTH_da025474c0c44edd99332dddb09cabe8/internal_photos/bs/2023/j/l/yuWhBvTH6CFIvGXG3PrA/sede-do-banco-central-do-brasil-em-brasilia.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>#113 - Gestão do crédito em situações especiais com Jive Investments</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Assista ao episódio em vídeo: https://www.youtube.com/live/jaIH5QIDS1QA oferta de investimentos alternativos, em especial de créditos mais estruturados, tem crescido no Brasil. E em um cenário adverso para o mercado de crédito no geral, quais são as oportunidades disponíveis em Special Situations?Para falar sobre as estruturas e oportunidades em Special Sits, convidamos Alexandre Cruz, sócio fundador e Mateus Tessler que é sócio e CIO responsável pela estratégia de Distressed e Special Sits na Jive Investments: gestora brasileira conhecida por ter comprado créditos “estressados”, créditos vencidos ou/e de baixa qualidade do famoso banco americano Lehman Brothers, após sua falência em 2008.-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------Investir com a XP Investimentos é fácil, basta criar o seu cadastro e em minutos você já pode começar a investir: http://bit.ly/41SHHkAAcompanhe todos os conteúdos da XP em https://t2m.io/ZAqGh0uParticipe do canal do Telegram para estar sempre atualizado: https://t.me/xp_investimentosConfira mais conteúdos também através do nosso Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/expertxp/Deixe seu comentário, inscreva-se no canal e ative as notificações para receber todas as novidades: https://bit.ly/3lUQQWW.</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a283507746679a9ca9cb49c9e" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Powell, Opening Remarks</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Speech At the Economic Club of New York Luncheon, New York, New York</description>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.remessaonline.com.br/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/o-que-e-fed-1170x781.jpg.optimal.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Can China Catch Up with Greece?</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>China&#39;s leader Xi Jinping recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fmprc.gov.cn/eng/zxxx_662805/202210/t20221025_10791908.html&quot;&gt;laid out&lt;/a&gt; the goal of reaching the per capita income of &quot;a mid-level developed country by 2035.&quot; Is this goal likely to be achieved? Not in our view. Continued rapid growth faces mounting headwinds from population aging and from diminishing returns to China&#39;s investment-centered growth model. Additional impediments to growth appear to be building, including a turn     toward increased state management of the economy, the   crystallization of legacy credit issues in real estate and other sectors, and limits on access to key foreign technologies. Even given generous assumptions concerning future growth fundamentals, China appears likely to close only a fraction of the gap with high-income countries in the years ahead.</description>
  <category>Notícias</category>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://d3g9pb5nvr3u7.cloudfront.net/sites/59dd2d9d016a1b2d929cd15b/-1445257209/256.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Borrower Expectations for the Return of Student Loan Repayment</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>After forty-three months of forbearance, the pause on federal student loan payments has ended. Originally enacted at the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic in March 2020, the administrative forbearance and interest waiver lasted until September 1, 2023, and borrowers’ monthly payments resumed this month. As discussed in an &lt;a href=&quot;https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2023/10/an-update-on-the-health-of-the-u-s-consumer&quot;&gt;accompanying post&lt;/a&gt;, the pause on student loan payments afforded borrowers over $260 billion in waived payments throughout the pandemic, supporting borrowers’ consumption and savings over the last three years. In this post, we analyze responses of student loan borrowers to special questions in the August 2023 SCE Household Spending Survey designed to gauge the expected impact of the payment resumption on future spending growth, the risk of credit delinquency for borrowers, and the economy at large. The findings suggest that the payment resumption will have a relatively small overall effect on consumption, on the order of a 0.1 percentage point reduction in aggregate spending from August levels, and a (delayed) return of student loan delinquency rates back to pre-pandemic levels. Across groups, we see little variation in spending responses but find that low-income borrowers, female borrowers, those with less than a bachelor’s degree, and those who were not in repayment before the pandemic expect the highest likelihood of missed student loan payments.</description>
  <category>Notícias</category>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://d3g9pb5nvr3u7.cloudfront.net/sites/59dd2d9d016a1b2d929cd15b/-1445257209/256.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>BC - Focus - Relatório de Mercado - 13/10/2023</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>O Relatório Focus resume as estatísticas calculadas considerando as expectativas de mercado coletadas até a sexta-feira anterior à sua divulgação. Ele é divulgado toda segunda-feira. O relatório traz a evolução gráfica e o comportamento semanal das projeções para índices de preços, atividade econômica, câmbio, taxa Selic, entre outros indicadores. As projeções são do mercado, não do BC.</description>
  <category>Bacen</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://s2-oglobo.glbimg.com/4Ugd1L8ibkhIE19fug0Uch8n_yI=/0x0:2000x1323/888x0/smart/filters:strip_icc()/i.s3.glbimg.com/v1/AUTH_da025474c0c44edd99332dddb09cabe8/internal_photos/bs/2023/j/l/yuWhBvTH6CFIvGXG3PrA/sede-do-banco-central-do-brasil-em-brasilia.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>FEDS Paper: Measuring Interest Rate Risk Management by Financial Institutions</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/celso-brunetti.htm&quot;&gt;Celso Brunetti&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/nathan-foley-fisher.htm&quot;&gt;Nathan Foley-Fisher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/stephane-verani.htm&quot;&gt;St&amp;eacute;phane Verani&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Financial intermediaries manage myriad interest rate risk exposures. We propose a new method to measure financial intermediaries&#39; residual interest rate risk using high-frequency financial market data. Our method exploits all available high-frequency information and is valid under extremely weak assumptions. Applying the method to U.S. life insurers, we find their interest rate risk management strategies are generally effective. However, life insurers are more sensitive to changes in long-term interest rates than property and casualty insurers. We show that the term premium helps to explain the difference in sensitivities between the two types of insurer.</description>
  <category>Papers</category>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://einvestidor.estadao.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/fed-the-federal-reserve-system-the-central-bankin-2023-01-17-05-21-55-utc-2_130320230113.jpg.webp" medium="image" type="image/webp"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>A Few Laws of Getting Rich</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Measuring wealth is easy. You just count it up. Measuring some of the downsides of wealth is so much harder and more nuanced. They can be so nuanced and hard to measure that many people won’t even believe they exist. A downside to wealth? How could that possibly be? Let me propose that the absurdity of talking about the downside of wealth is part of why wealth doesn’t tend to make people as happy as they thought it would. When the benefits of money are so obvious but the downsides are so subtle, the downsides you didn’t anticipate can be more jarring than the benefits you expected. I want more money, of course. Almost everyone does, albeit for different reasons. This is not an anti-wealth list -- just a collection of subtle downsides that are easy to ignore, and so common you may as well call them the only true laws of getting rich.</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a31625160ddb282e12cf71f98" medium="image"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>FEDS Paper: Flood Risk Mapping and the Distributional Impacts of Climate Information</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Joakim A. Weill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This paper examines the provision of official flood risk information in the United States and its distributional impacts on residential flood insurance take-up. Assembling all flood maps produced after Hurricane Katrina, I document that updated maps decreased the number of properties zoned in high-risk floodplains and incorrectly omitted five million properties, primarily in neighborhoods with more Black and Hispanic residents. Leveraging the staggered timing of map updates, I estimate they decreased flood insurance take-up and exacerbated racial disparities in insurance coverage. Correcting flood maps could increase welfare by $20 billion annually, but past map updates distorted risk and price signals.</description>
  <category>Papers</category>
  <category>FED</category>
  <category>BC</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://einvestidor.estadao.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/fed-the-federal-reserve-system-the-central-bankin-2023-01-17-05-21-55-utc-2_130320230113.jpg.webp" medium="image" type="image/webp"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>#112 - Crédito privado e a infraestrutura brasileira com a JGP</title>
  <link>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</link>
  <description>Assista ao episódio em vídeo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AUaxi0PSJmAInvestir com a XP Investimentos é fácil, basta criar o seu cadastro e em minutos você já pode começar a investir: http://bit.ly/41SHHkAAcompanhe todos os conteúdos da XP em https://t2m.io/ZAqGh0uParticipe do canal do Telegram para estar sempre atualizado: https://t.me/xp_investimentosConfira mais conteúdos também através do nosso Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/expertxp/</description>
  <category>Podcasts</category>
  <guid>https://github.com/lucas-leme/blog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a3f0df2111c7eb8fb220a2a8a" medium="image"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
